Henry Y. Porter Theater Memorabilia Collection MS003
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Artists and other celebrities; prints, photographs, and artifacts, 1722 -- 1990; 1880 -- 1920; MS003.001; 33.95 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 4 Digital Object(s)
  - Singers, 8x10s, tenors, all signed, 1880 -- 1960; MS003.001.034
    - Paul Althouse (1889-1954), American tenor, and his pupil, Alexander Eddy (1910-1974), 1940 -- 1950; MS003.001.034.00004 (Box 34)
    - Angelo Bada (1875-1941), Italian tenor, 1935; MS003.001.034.00005 (Box 34)
    - Angelo Bada (1875-1941), Italian tenor, 1935; MS003.001.034.00006 (Box 34)
    - Dan Beddoe (1863-1937), American tenor, 1923; MS003.001.034.00007 (Box 34)
    - Joseph Bentonelli (1900-1975), American tenor, 1930 -- 1950; MS003.001.034.00008 (Box 34)
    - Jussi Bjoerling (1911-1960), Swedish tenor, 1939; MS003.001.034.00009 (Box 34)
    - Jussi Bjoerling (1911-1960), Swedish tenor, 1946; MS003.001.034.00010 (Box 34)
    - Alessandro Bonci (1870-1940), Italian tenor, 1929; MS003.001.034.00011 (Box 34)
    - Alessandro Bonci (1870-1940), Italian tenor, 1925; MS003.001.034.00012 (Box 34)
    - Max Bloch (1890-1930), German tenor, 1925; MS003.001.034.00013 (Box 34)
    - Dino Borgioli (1891-1960), Italian tenor, 1930 -- 1950; MS003.001.034.00014 (Box 34)
    - Arthur Carron (1901-1967), English tenor, 1950; MS003.001.034.00015 (Box 34)
    - Arthur Carron (1901-1967), English tenor, 1950; MS003.001.034.00016 (Box 34)
    - Mario Chamlee (1892-1966), American tenor, 1920 -- 1940; MS003.001.034.00017 (Box 34)
    - Mario Chamlee (1892-1966), American tenor, 1920 -- 1940; MS003.001.034.00018 (Box 34)
    - Guido Ciccolini (1879-1963), Italian tenor, 1916; MS003.001.034.00019 (Box 34)
    - Eugene Conley (1908-1981), American tenor, 1940 -- 1950; MS003.001.034.00020 (Box 34)
    - Eugene Conley (1908-1981), American tenor, 1940 -- 1960; MS003.001.034.00021 (Box 34)
    - Hans Clemens (1891-1959), German tenor, 1936; MS003.001.034.00022 (Box 34)
    - Richard Crooks (1900-1972), American tenor, 1925; MS003.001.034.00023 (Box 34)
    - Richard Crooks (1900-1972), American tenor, 1935; MS003.001.034.00024 (Box 34)
    - Richard Crooks (1900-1972), American tenor, 1940; MS003.001.034.00025 (Box 34)
    - Charles Dalmores (1871-1939), French tenor, 1923; MS003.001.034.00026 (Box 34)
    - Donald Dame (1917-1958), American tenor, 1950; MS003.001.034.00027 (Box 34)
    - Ben Davies (1858-1943), Welsh tenor, 1890 -- 1910; MS003.001.034.00028 (Box 34)
    - Bernardo De Murio (1881-1955), Italian tenor, 1925; MS003.001.034.00029 (Box 34)
    - Alessio De Paulis (1893-1964), Italian tenor, 1939; MS003.001.034.00030 (Box 34)
    - Rafaelo Diaz (1883-1943), American tenor, 1920 -- 1930; MS003.001.034.00031 (Box 34)
    - Andreas Dippel (1866-1935), German tenor, 1890 -- 1912; MS003.001.034.00032 (Box 34)
    - John Finnegan, tenor soloist, 1923; MS003.001.034.00033 (Box 34)
    - John Garris (1911-1949), German tenor, 1943; MS003.001.034.00034 (Box 34)
    - Dan Gridley (1891-1936), American tenor, 1935; MS003.001.034.00035 (Box 34)
    - Beniamino Gigli (1890-1957), Italian tenor, 1922; MS003.001.034.00036 (Box 34)
    - Beniamino Gigli (1890-1957), Italian tenor, 1939; MS003.001.034.00037 (Box 34)
    - Arthur Hackett (1884-1969), American tenor, 1910 -- 1925; MS003.001.034.00038 (Box 34)
    - Charles Hackett (1889-1942), American tenor, 1935; MS003.001.034.00039 (Box 34)
    - Charles Hackett (1889-1942), American tenor, 1930 -- 1940; MS003.001.034.00040 (Box 34)
    - Charles Hackett (1889-1942), American tenor, 1924; MS003.001.034.00041 (Box 34)
    - George Hamlin (1869-1923), American tenor, 1922; MS003.001.034.00042 (Box 34)
    - Orville Harrold (1877?-1933), American tenor, 1928; MS003.001.034.00043 (Box 34)
    - Orville Harrold (1877?-1933), American tenor, 1900 -- 1930; MS003.001.034.00044 (Box 34)
    - Carl Hartmann (1895-1969), German tenor, 1937 -- 1938; MS003.001.034.00045 (Box 34)
    - Roland Hayes (1887-1977), American tenor, 1925; MS003.001.034.00046 (Box 34)
    - Roland Hayes (1887-1977), American tenor, 1955; MS003.001.034.00047 (Box 34)
    - Frederick Jagel (1897-1982), American tenor, 1928; MS003.001.034.00048 (Box 34)
    - Frederick Jagel (1897-1982), American tenor, 1932 -- 1933; MS003.001.034.00049 (Box 34)
    - Frederick Jagel (1897-1982), American tenor, 1937; MS003.001.034.00050 (Box 34)
    - Frederick Jagel (1897-1982), American tenor, 1941; MS003.001.034.00051 (Box 34)
    - Raoul Jobin (1906-1974), Canadian tenor, 1940 -- 1950; MS003.001.034.00052 (Box 34)
    - Edward Johnson (1878-1959), Canadian tenor, 1910 -- 1930; MS003.001.034.00053 (Box 34)
    - Edward Johnson (1878-1959), Canadian tenor, 1900 -- 1930; MS003.001.034.00054 (Box 34)
    - Theo Karle (Johnston), (1893-1972), American tenor, 1920 -- 1930; MS003.001.034.00055 (Box 34)
    - Jan Kiepura (1902-1986), Polish tenor, 1938; MS003.001.034.00056 (Box 34)
    - Morgan Kingston (1881-1936), English tenor, 1920 -- 1935; MS003.001.034.00057 (Box 34)
    - Charles Kullman (1903-1983), American tenor, 1936; MS003.001.034.00058 (Box 34)
    - Eyverid Laholm (1894-1958), American tenor, 1939; MS003.001.034.00059 (Box 34)
    - Forrest Lamont (1881-1937), American tenor, 1910 -- 1930; MS003.001.034.00060 (Box 34)
    - Bruno Landi (1900-1968), Italian tenor, 1941; MS003.001.034.00061 (Box 34)
    - Bruno Landi (1900-1968), Italian tenor, 1938; MS003.001.034.00062 (Box 34)
    - Mario Louza (1921-1959), American tenor, MS003.001.034.00063 (Box 34)
    - Hipolito Lazaro (1889-1974), Spanish tenor, 1920 -- 1950; MS003.001.034.00064 (Box 34)
    - Hipolito Lazaro (1889-1974), Spanish tenor, 1930; MS003.001.034.00065 (Box 34)
    - Hipolito Lazaro (1889-1974), Spanish tenor, 1920; MS003.001.034.00066 (Box 34)
    - Francis Maclemian (1879-1935), American tenor, and his wife, Florence Easton (1884-1955), English soprano, 1916 -- 1918; MS003.001.034.00067 (Box 34)
    - Rene Maison (1895-1962), Belgian tenor, 1939; MS003.001.034.00068 (Box 34)
    - Rene Maison (1895-1962), Belgian tenor, 1928 -- 1929; MS003.001.034.00069 (Box 34)
    - Anthony Marlowe (1810-1962), American tenor, 1910; MS003.001.034.00070 (Box 34)
    - Charles Marshall (1886-1951), American tenor, 1928; MS003.001.034.00071 (Box 34)
    - Charles Marshall (1886-1951), American tenor, 1915; MS003.001.034.00072 (Box 34)
    - Riccardo Martin (1879-1952), American tenor, 1900 -- 1920; MS003.001.034.00073 (Box 34)
      Inscription on front reads "in friendly remembrance of Riccardo Martion." Reverse side reads: "Riccardo Martin, 1879-1952, American Tenor. Victa Records."
      Opera.; Opera singers; Martin, Riccardo, 1874-1952
    - Riccardo Martin (1879-1952), American tenor, 1921 -- 1924; MS003.001.034.00074 (Box 34)
      Inscription on front reads: "To Henry Y. Porter in friendly remembrance of New York 1924 Riccardo Martin." Inscription on back reads" Riccardo Martin, 1879-1952, American Tenor formerly with Metropolitan and Chicago Opera cos."
    - Riccardo Martin (1879-1952), American tenor, 1915; MS003.001.034.00075 (Box 34)
      Inscription on front reads: "To W. C. Hill in friendly remembrance of Riccardo Martin. Boston 24 Nov. 1915. Matzene Chicago." Inscription on back reads: "Riccardo Martin, Dramatic tenor Boston G. rand Opera Co. in conjunction with Pavlows Imperial Balet Russo."
    - Riccardo Martin (1879-1952), American tenor, 1911; MS003.001.034.00076 (Box 34)
      Inscription on front reads: "To Charles L. Wagner in friendly remembrance of Riccardo Martin, New York, 1911.
    - Giovanni Martinelli (1885-1969), Italian tenor, 1922; MS003.001.034.00077 (Box 34)
    - Giovanni Martinelli (1885-1969), Italian tenor, 1924; MS003.001.034.00078 (Box 34)
    - Giovanni Martinelli (1885-1969), Italian tenor, 1926; MS003.001.034.00079 (Box 34)
    - Giovanni Martinelli (1885-1969), Italian tenor, 1931; MS003.001.034.00080 (Box 34)
    - Nino Martini (1905-1976), Italian tenor, 1940 -- 1950; MS003.001.034.00081 (Box 34)
    - Lauritz Melchior (1890-1973), Danish tenor, 1935; MS003.001.034.00082 (Box 34)
    - Lauritz Melchior (1890-1973), Danish tenor, 1950; MS003.001.034.00083 (Box 34)
    - James Melton (1904-1961), American tenor, 1940 -- 1950; MS003.001.034.00084 (Box 34)
    - Reed Miller, American tenor, 1890 -- 1930; MS003.001.034.00085 (Box 34)
    - Jose Mojica (1896-1974), Mexican tenor, 1920 -- 1940; MS003.001.034.00086 (Box 34)
    - Jose Mojica (1896-1974), Mexican tenor, 1925; MS003.001.034.00087 (Box 34)
    - Lucien Muratore (1878-1954), French tenor, 1910 -- 1930; MS003.001.034.00088 (Box 34)
    - Lucien Muratore (1878-1954), French tenor, 1900 -- 1920; MS003.001.034.00089 (Box 34)
    - Lambert Murphy (1885-1954), American tenor, 1924; MS003.001.034.00090 (Box 34)
    - Lodovico Alivieri (1886-1948), Italian tenor, 1940; MS003.001.034.00091 (Box 34)
    - Giordano Paltrinieri (1880-1970), Italian tenor, 1934; MS003.001.034.00092 (Box 34)
    - Jan Peerce (1904-1984), American tenor, 1940 -- 1950; MS003.001.034.00093 (Box 34)
    - George Rasely (1891-1965), American tenor, 1941; MS003.001.034.00094 (Box 34)
    - Sydney Raynor (1895-1981), American tenor, 1940 -- 1950; MS003.001.034.00095 (Box 34)
    - John Sirus Reeves (1818-1900), English tenor, 1880 -- 1900; MS003.001.034.00096 (Box 34)
    - Paul Reimers (1878-1942), German tenor, 1922; MS003.001.034.00097 (Box 34)
    - Albert Reiss (1869-1940), German tenor, 1900 -- 1920; MS003.001.034.00098 (Box 34)
    - Cantor Josef Rosenblatt, Hungarian tenor, 1900 -- 1940; MS003.001.034.00099 (Box 34)
    - Tito Schipa (1889-1965), Italian tenor, 1929; MS003.001.034.00100 (Box 34)
    - Armand Tokatyan (1898-1960), Armenian tenor, 1936; MS003.001.034.00101 (Box 34)
    - Richard Tucker (1913-1975), American tenor, 1940 -- 1960; MS003.001.034.00102 (Box 34)
    - Richard Tucker (1913-1975), American tenor, 1940 -- 1960; MS003.001.034.00103 (Box 34)
    - Richard Tucker (1913-1975), American tenor, 1960; MS003.001.034.00104 (Box 34)
    - Marek Windheim (1895-1960), Polish tenor, 1935; MS003.001.034.00105 (Box 34)
    - Giovanni Zentello (1876-1949), Italian tenor, 1943; MS003.001.034.00106 (Box 34)
    - Giovanni Zentello (1876-1949), Italian tenor, 1900 -- 1920; MS003.001.034.00107 (Box 34)
    - Giovanni Zentello (1876-1949), Italian tenor, 1915; MS003.001.034.00108 (Box 34)
    - Nicola Zerola, Italian tenor, 1928; MS003.001.034.00109 (Box 34)
    - Nicola Zerola, Italian tenor, 1928; MS003.001.034.00110 (Box 34)
  - Theatre and music personalities, 8x10s, all signed, 1900 -- 1975; MS003.001.035
    - George Arliss (1868-1946), English actor, 1900 -- 1920; MS003.001.035.00001 (Box 35)
    - George Arliss (1868-1946), English actor as Shylock in "The Merchant of Venice," 1928, MS003.001.035.00002 (Box 35)
      From the 1928 Broadway production of The Merchant of Venice (see also 35:03). Signed.
    - Peggy Wood (1892-1978), American actress as Portia in "The Merchant of Venice," 1928, MS003.001.035.00003 (Box 35)
      From the 1928 Broadway production of The Merchant of Venice (see also 35:02). Signed.
    - Katharine Cornell (1898-1967), American actress as Juliet in "Romeo and Juliet," 1934, MS003.001.035.00004 (Box 35)
      From the 1934 Broadway production of Romeo and Juliet (see also 35:05). Signed.
    - Basil Rathbone (1892-1967), English actor as Romeo in "Romeo and Juliet," 1934, MS003.001.035.00005 (Box 35)
      From the 1934 Broadway production of Romeo and Juliet (see also 35:04). Signed.
    - Katharine Cornell (1898-1974), as Cleopatra in "Antony and Cleopatra," 1947-48, 1947 -- 1948; MS003.001.035.00006 (Box 35)
      From the 1947-48 Broadway production of Antony and Cleopatra (see also 35:07). Signed.
    - Godfrey Teale (1884-1953), English actor as Antony in "Antony and Cleopatra," 1947-48, 1947 -- 1948; MS003.001.035.00007 (Box 35)
      From the 1947-48 Broadway production of Antony and Cleopatra (see also 35:06). Signed.
    - Jane Cowl (1885-1950), American actress as Juliet in "Romeo and Juliet," 1924, MS003.001.035.00008 (Box 35)
    - Maurice Evans (1901-1989), English actor as Macbeth in "Macbeth," 1941-42, 1941 -- 1942; MS003.001.035.00009 (Box 35)
      From the 1941-42 Broadway production of Macbeth (see also 35:10). Signed.
    - Dame Judith Anderson (1898-1992), Australian actress as Lady Macbeth in "Macbeth," 1942, 1941 -- 1942; MS003.001.035.00010 (Box 35)
      From the 1941-42 Broadway production of Macbeth (see also 35:09). Signed.
    - Maurice Evans (1901-1989), as King Richard in "Richard II," ca. 1940, MS003.001.035.00011 (Box 35)
    - John Gielgud (1904-2000), English actor as Hamlet in "Hamlet," in 1936-37, 1936 -- 1937; MS003.001.035.00012 (Box 35)
      From the 1936-37 Broadway production of Hamlet (see also 35:13). Signed.
    - Lillian Gish (1896-1993), American actress as Desdemona in "Hamlet," 1938, MS003.001.035.00013 (Box 35)
      From the 1936-37 Broadway production of Hamlet (see also 35:12). Signed.
    - Walter Hampden (1879-1955), American actor as "Hamlet" in Hamlet, 1925; MS003.001.035.00014 (Box 35)
    - Lyn Harding (1867-1952), Welsh actor as Macbeth in "Macbeth," 1928, MS003.001.035.00015 (Box 35)
      From the 1928 Broadway production of Macbeth (see also 35:16). Signed.
    - Florence Reed (1883-1967), American actress as Lady Macbeth in "Macbeth," 1939, MS003.001.035.00016 (Box 35)
      From the 1928 Broadway production of Macbeth (see also 35:15). Signed.
    - Helen Hayes (1900-1993), American actress as Portia in "The Merchant of Venice," 1939, MS003.001.035.00017 (Box 35)
    - Leslie Howard (1893-1943), English actor as Hamlet in "Hamlet," 1936, MS003.001.035.00018 (Box 35)
      From the 1936 Broadway production of Hamlet. Signed.
    - Walter Huston (1884-1950), Canadian actor as Othello in "Othello," 1937, MS003.001.035.00019 (Box 35)
      From the 1937 Broadway production of Othello (see also 35:20). Signed.
    - Nan Sunderland, American actress as Desdemona in "Othello," 1937, MS003.001.035.00020 (Box 35)
      From the 1937 Broadway production of Othello (see also 35:19). Signed.
    - Alfred Lunt (1892-1977), American actor as Petruchio in "The Taming of the Shrew," ca. 1935, MS003.001.035.00021 (Box 35)
    - Lynn Fontanne (1887-1983), English actress as Katherine in "The Taming of the Shrew," ca. 1935, MS003.001.035.00022 (Box 35)
    - Burgess Meredith (1909-1997), American actor as Prince Hal in "Five Kings," ca. 1940, MS003.001.035.00023 (Box 35)
    - Sir Laurence Olivier (1907-1989), English actor as Romeo in "Romeo and Juliet," 1940, MS003.001.035.00024 (Box 35)
      From the 1940 Broadway production of Romeo and Juliet (see also 35:25-26). Signed.
    - Vivien Leigh (1913-1967), English actress as Juliet in "Romeo and Juliet," 1940, MS003.001.035.00025 (Box 35)
      From the 1940 Broadway production of Romeo and Juliet (see also 35:24, 26). Signed.
    - Dame May Whitty (1865-1948), English actress as the nurse in "Romeo and Juliet," 1940, MS003.001.035.00026 (Box 35)
      From the 1940 Broadway production of Romeo and Juliet (see also 35:24-25). Signed.
    - Paul Robeson (1898-1976), American actor as Othello in "Othello," 1943-44, 1943 -- 1944; MS003.001.035.00027 (Box 35)
      From the 1943-44 Broadway production of Othello (see also 35:28-30, 74). Signed.
    - Uta Hagen (1919- ), German actress as Desdemona in "Othello," 1943-44, 1943 -- 1944; MS003.001.035.00028 (Box 35)
      From the 1943-44 Broadway production of Othello (see also 35:27, 29, 30, 74). Signed.
    - Jose Ferrer (1909-92), Puerto Rican actor as Iago in "Othello," 1943-44, 1943 -- 1944; MS003.001.035.00029 (Box 35)
      From the 1943-44 Broadway production of Othello (see also 35:27, 28, 30, 74). Signed.
    - Margaret Webster (1905-72), American actress as Emilia in "Othello," 1943-44, 1943 -- 1944; MS003.001.035.00030 (Box 35)
      From the 1943-44 Broadway production of Othello (see also 35:27-29, 74). Signed.
    - Otis Skinner (1858-1942), American actor as Shylock in "The Merchant of Venice," 1939, MS003.001.035.00031 (Box 35)
    - Maude Adams (1872-1953), American actress as Portia in "The Merchant of Venice," 1931, MS003.001.035.00032 (Box 35)
    - Edward H. Sothern (1859-1933), American actor, 1900 -- 1930; MS003.001.035.00033 (Box 35)
    - Julia Marlowe (1865-1950), English actress as Juliet in "Romeo and Juliet," ca. 1910, MS003.001.035.00034 (Box 35)
    - Fred Astaire (1899-1987), American dancer and actor, 1940; MS003.001.035.00035 (Box 35)
    - Lionel Barrymore (1878-1954), American actor, 1930; MS003.001.035.00036 (Box 35)
    - Eddie Cantor (1892-1964), American comedian, 1930; MS003.001.035.00037 (Box 35)
    - Frank Crumit (1889-1943), American actor and Julia Sanderson (1887-1975), American actress, his wife, 1930; MS003.001.035.00038 (Box 35)
    - Walter E. Disney (1901-1966), American producer of animated sound cartoons, 1950; MS003.001.035.00039 (Box 35)
    - Martyn Green (1899-1975), English singer and actor, 1960; MS003.001.035.00040 (Box 35)
    - Sir Harry Lauder (1870-1950), Scotch comedian, 1910; MS003.001.035.00041 (Box 35)
    - Beatrice Lillie (1898-1989), Canadian comedienne, 1930; MS003.001.035.00042 (Box 35)
    - Skedge Miller (1918- ), American actor, 1950; MS003.001.035.00043 (Box 35)
    - Douglass Montgomery (1908-1966), American actor, 1940; MS003.001.035.00044 (Box 35)
    - Charles Nolte (1926- ), American actor, 1960; MS003.001.035.00045 (Box 35)
    - Charles Nolte (1926- ), American actor, 1960; MS003.001.035.00046 (Box 35)
    - Charles Nolte (1926- ), American actor with Charlton Heston and Martha Scott in "Design for a Stained Glass Window," 1950, MS003.001.035.00047 (Box 35)
    - Tyrone Power (1915-1958), American actor, and Linda Darnell (1921-1965), American actress, 1950; MS003.001.035.00048 (Box 35)
    - Pat Rooney, Sr. (1880-1962), American dance and actor, 1940; MS003.001.035.00049 (Box 35)
    - Annunzio Mantovani (1905- ), English conductor, 1960; MS003.001.035.00050 (Box 35)
    - Lawrence Welk (1903-1992), American conductor, 1965; MS003.001.035.00051 (Box 35)
    - Paul Whiteman (1890-1967), American conductor, 1940; MS003.001.035.00052 (Box 35)
    - Irving Berlin (1888-1989), American composer, 1930; MS003.001.035.00053 (Box 35)
    - Betty Comden (1919- ), and Adolph Green (1915- ), American librettists and collaborators, 1955; MS003.001.035.00054 (Box 35)
    - Sir Noel Coward (1899-1973), English composer, 1935; MS003.001.035.00055 (Box 35)
    - Rudolph Friml (1879-1972), Bohemian composer, 1940; MS003.001.035.00056 (Box 35)
    - Rudolph Friml (1879-1972), Bohemian composer, 1930; MS003.001.035.00057 (Box 35)
    - Otto Harbach (1873-1963), American librettist, 1950; MS003.001.035.00058 (Box 35)
    - Jerome Kern (1885-1945), American compser, 1939; MS003.001.035.00059 (Box 35)
    - Alan Jay Lerner (1918-86), American librettist, 1960; MS003.001.035.00060 (Box 35)
    - Frederick Loewe (1901-88) Austrian composer, 1950; MS003.001.035.00061 (Box 35)
    - Richard Rodgers (1902-1979), American compser, 1960; MS003.001.035.00062 (Box 35)
    - Oscar Hammerstein (1895-1960), American librettist, 1950; MS003.001.035.00063 (Box 35)
    - Sigmund Romberg (1887-1951), Hungarian composer and conductor, 1940; MS003.001.035.00064 (Box 35)
    - Rudolf Nureyev (1938-1993), Russian ballet dancer, 1970; MS003.001.035.00065 (Box 35)
    - Fernando Bujones (1955- ), ballet dancer, 1960 -- 1975; MS003.001.035.00066 (Box 35)
    - Arleen Hackett, actress, 1900 -- 1940; MS003.001.035.00067 (Box 35)
    - Richard Chamberlain (1935- ), American actor, 1970; MS003.001.035.00068 (Box 35)
    - Jimmy Durante (1893-1980), American actor and comedian, 1970; MS003.001.035.00069 (Box 35)
    - Mae West (1892-1980), American stage and screen actress, 1940; MS003.001.035.00070 (Box 35)
    - Jessica Dragonette (?-1980), American soprano, 1920 -- 1940; MS003.001.035.00071 (Box 35)
    - Fred Waring and his Pennsylvanians, 1920 -- 1960; MS003.001.035.00072 (Box 35)
    - Hoagy Carmichael (1899-1981), American composer and actor, 1955; MS003.001.035.00073 (Box 35)
    - Jose Ferrer and Jack Manning, 1943 -- 1944; MS003.001.035.00074 (Box 35)
      Jose Ferrer as 'Iago' and Jack Manning as 'Roderigo' from the 1943-44 Broadway production of Othello with Paul Robeson in the lead role (see also 35:27-30). Signed by both.
  - Cabinet cards, tenors, baritones, basses, conductors and impresarios, all signed, 1890 -- 1940; MS003.001.036.001 (Box 36)
  - Cabinet cards, sopranos, contraltos, musicians and composers, all signed, 1900 -- 1940; MS003.001.037.001 (Box 37)
  - 19th century actors, singers and personalities, 8x10s mounted on cardstock, MS003.001.038
    - Kate Rorke, English actress (1866-1945), MS003.001.038.00001 (Box 38)
      aka: Mrs. E.W. Gardiner.
      Porter, Henry Y.
    - Ellen Wallis, English Actress (1856-1940), MS003.001.038.00002 (Box 38)
      aka: Mrs. John Lancaster
    - Mrs. Humphrey Ward, English Novelist, (1851-1920), MS003.001.038.00003 (Box 38)
    - Winifred Emery, English Actress (1862-1924), MS003.001.038.00004 (Box 38)
      aka: Mrs Cyril Maude
    - Alfred Lord Tennyson, English Poet (1809-92), MS003.001.038.00005 (Box 38)
      Poet Laureate 1850-1892
    - Thomas Hardy, English novelist and playwright (1840-1928), MS003.001.038.00006 (Box 38)
      "Tess of the d'Urbervilles"
    - Sir Henry Rider Haggard, English Novelist (1856-1925), MS003.001.038.00007 (Box 38)
    - Genevieve Ward, American singer and actress (1833-1922), MS003.001.038.00008 (Box 38)
    - Sir Charles Wyndham, English Actor and Manager (1837-1919), MS003.001.038.00009 (Box 38)
      aka: Charles Culverwell
    - Sir John Hare, English actor and manager (1844-1921), MS003.001.038.00010 (Box 38)
      aka: John Fairs
    - Dame Madge Kendal (1849-1935) and William Hunter Kendal (1843-1917), English actors, MS003.001.038.00011 (Box 38)
      Dame Madge Kendal aka: Margaret Shafto Robertson (Porter is incorrect). William Hunter Kendal aka: William Hunter Grimston.
    - John Lawrence Toole, English comedian, (1830-1906), MS003.001.038.00012 (Box 38)
    - Agnes Huntington, American contralto, (1864-1953), MS003.001.038.00013 (Box 38)
      aka: Mrs. Paul D. Crowath
    - Dame Ellen Terry, English actress, (1847-1928), MS003.001.038.00014 (Box 38)
      Associate of Henry Irving. She was created Dame Grand Cross, Order of the British Empire in 1925.
    - Mary Moore, English actress, (1862-1931), MS003.001.038.00015 (Box 38)
      aka: Mrs. Charles Wyndham
    - Clara Schumann, German pianist, (1819-96), MS003.001.038.00016 (Box 38)
      Wife of Robert Schumann, composer.
    - Sir Johnston Forbes-Robertson, English actor, (1853-1937), MS003.001.038.00017 (Box 38)
    - Sir Henry Irving, English actor, (1838-1905), MS003.001.038.00018 (Box 38)
      Professionally associated with Ellen Terry 1878-1902, made eight American tours. Knighted 1895, the first actor to be so honored. Buried in Westminster Abbey.
    - Julia Neilson English actress, (1868-1957), MS003.001.038.00019 (Box 38)
      Married Fred Terry, brother of Ellen Terry.
    - Mrs. John Wood, English actress, (1831-1915), MS003.001.038.00020 (Box 38)
      aka: Matilda Vining.
    - Mary Antoinette Anderson, American actress, (1859-1940), MS003.001.038.00021 (Box 38)
      Debut, Louisville, KY in 1875. Married Antonio de Navano in 1889 and retired from the stage.
    - Fanny Bernard-Beere, English actress, (1857-1915), MS003.001.038.00022 (Box 38)
    - Sir Arthur Wing Pinero, English dramatist (1855-1934), MS003.001.038.00023 (Box 38)
      Wrote: "The Second Mrs. Tanqueray," The Gay Lord Quex," "The Enchanted Cottage," etc.
    - Sir Hall Caine, English novelist and playwright, (1853-1931), MS003.001.038.00024 (Box 38)
      Wrote: "The Christian," "The Woman Thou gavest Me," etc.